Hello, and welcome back to Adobe Chats
B2B Marketing Demystified Asia edition.
I'm your host Joe Escobedo.
And with me today is Vishwash Guar,
who is the head of customer and
digital experience at FWD  Insurance.
Thanks so much for being the
show Vishwash . Thank you, Joe.
for inviting me, looking forward
to an exciting conversation.
Absolutely.
Really excited about today's conversation.
Because today we talking about
marketing in financial services.
Our focus is on customers.
Whatever we do, whether we are creating a
sales process or we are creating a service
process, or, uh, we are creating a simple
webpage that everything is for customers.
And we craft the story so that we
can understand that what is the kind
of the behavior people are showing?
What is the kind of the reflection
of emotions they might have?
So our web pages, our
sales flows are on that.
So data tells us about that, what
the customers are looking for,
then we create the products or the
content or the services, um, with
that using the factory energy.
So being a digital direct company, it's
very important for us to sell online and
service online and being available online.
So in that space and our
entire shop is our website.
You enter in a showroom,
which is a physical showroom.
And if that is so messy that
people can't find the kind of the
shoes or things they are looking
for, then it becomes difficult.
We learn from, uh, the offline
world and  how people actually
behave in the offline world.
And then, um, we implemented to
understand the various interactions of
our customers with the website, and then
by this tracking we understood okay.
Uh, these are the possible friction
points which are causing the difficulty.
Typically for a car insurance.
How you see happens, that you
enter your details and after you
enter details, you actually shown
two or three different plans.
After you tell me about your car.
I show you three different options.
And I say, Joe, please take one of them.
Then you'll be confused.
So what we did here, we learned
from the data, um, that what people
are actually buying more and what
are the rationales of buying more?
And of course, like what kind of
add-ons are the riders they take?
So we call that social proof and we
started making recommendations by
making such simple recommendations,
our conversion sales improved.
Also, we were able to actually help
more customers in, um, in buying
online in a very simplistic manner.
This was one of the example of how
we improve the conversion rate.
Emotion side.
Very important.
So that's why uh, our
chat bot meme is Faith.
So we put a human face there, so she
moves her head here and there you'll
see the hair's flipping as well.
So, so as much as possible real
experience when people are actually
coming to a specific page, they have
some top, um, uh, questions as well.
So instead of letting them go
into the chat bot, ask those
questions and then getting the
answers, we are offering a start.
Okay.
These are the top five questions.
Most people ask to me.
Um, do you have any one of them
or ask me any of those questions.
Right now uh, one fifth of our
digital, um, interaction volume is
actually managed by this chat bot.
That's a lot in terms of savings in terms
of productivity and efficiency and so on.
Whenever it comes to
crafting an experience.
Um, our team is actually paying a lot of
attention, uh, to the customer emotions,
behaviors, and we are doing a lot of
research and insights when most of the
other companies are actually selling
online products in 20 or 30 minutes,
or maybe 14 minutes long journey.
We were selling it in eight minutes.
Someone will say, okay, we should
display this on our webpage.
And then we asked the
question, why do we need this.
From top to bottom everyone is
thinking from customer experience.
And that is one of the
things I'm really proud of.
So that reflects in the user
experience that is search and insight.
I think once again, I think some
really practical tips in here I'd love.
Once again, it goes back to
what you were saying at the very
beginning, thinking about it from
the customer's point of view.
That's one of my big pet peeves.
When I go to a website and going back to
your point about form fields, if you have
to go through a 20 or 30 fields  as a, as
a customer, you're already stressed out.
You want to jump off that, that website.
So asking the question with your
team, why are we putting in this
form , why are we adding this?
How can we do a little bit different?
How can we simplify the process?
And it goes to show you, you talked
about from 30 minutes to eight minutes
in terms of purchasing a specific
policy, which is incredibly fast
considering that the insurance and
financial service space is not the
easiest, um, concept to navigate
that you simplified it that much.
Right.
Focusing on UI UX is, is very impressive.
So well done to you and the team Vish.